Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Broadside, 1971-1999; (6 boxes)
  - Events [1 of 4], 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Aids Walk, Arcade Convention, GMU Anniversary, Alcohol Awareness Week, Cardboard Community, Clothesline Project, Blood Drive, Bloodmobile, Brother Jim, Body Awareness Week, Black Freshman Weekend, BSA Talent Show, Big Band Gala, Welcome Week, Bomb Threat and Crime Solvers
  - Events [2 of 4], 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Chinese New Year Festivities, Chalk the Walk,Drag Show, Fidelity Investments, Mason Ambassador Meeting, Self Defense Classes, Peace Corps Author Meeting, Bolshoi Symphony, Affirmation Action Debate, GLBT,GMU Dancers, Hunger Banquet, Home Coming Parade, Hispanic Gala Dinner, Higher Education Bond and Election Day, Hilal Group Presentation
  - Events [3 of 4], 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    International Week, Inaugural Service Prayer, It Won't Happen To Me, Job Fair, Live Jazz Band, Victim's Right Walk, Good Eating Habits, National Body Awareness Week, Health and Fitness Day, Poetry Reading, Choir, Conversation Hour, Got Milk Promotion, Student Dance, Mason Day, Mason Statue Unveiling, Mass Mutual, Marriot Scholarships, Mindfulness Lecture, Midnite Madness, Million Man and Woman March, Dance and Spirit of Native American
  - Events [4 of 4], 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Patriot Day, Sesame Street Live, Service Fair, Swing Dancers, Step Show-'98', Students-Scerbo, Mcrsinn, Slyvia, Tleena,I., Ya Boi and Kim, Taste of Fairfax, Theatre, Task Force on Drinking, Take Back the Night, Tom Horton's Activities, Technology Convention1998, Witch Watch 1996, Winnepeg Ballet, Warp Tour 1997
  - Faculty/Staff [1 of 2], 1980s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty/Staff [2 of 2], 1970s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Greeks, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gunston Hall, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Center Hall Staircase, Mason's Office, Dinning Room, Facade
  - History Department, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Honor Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Humanities Department, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Information Desk-Sub I, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Analysis, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - International and World Affairs Club, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Irish Fortnight Speaker, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Johnson Center, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Bookstore, Java George, Bank, Center Gallery, Food Stop, Construction, Library, Information Booth
  - Krug, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Liz Rieley, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Local Attractions and Restaurants, late 1990s (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Bombay Bistro, Pizza 'n' Pasta, Denny's, Golden Lion, Anita's, Patriot Books, Burke Lake Park, Washington D.C., Habana Village, Coco-Loco, Copacabana, Polly Esther, Red Moon Saloon, Vienna's Grille, The Bank, Lulu's, Fat Tuesday, Natural Mystics, The Golden Goose, Tyson's Corner, The Flower Gallery, Georgetown Park, Potomac Mills, Seasons, Old Navy, Picco's, Consignment, Fairfax Surf Shop, Pier One Imports, Paint Your Own Pottery, Crossroads, BlackCat, Bridges, Red Hot and Blue, Tastee, TT Reynolds, Mozzarella's Cafe, Dolce Vita, Rio Grande Cafe, Havabite Eatery, Hennessy's Cafe, Topkapi, BlackEyed Pea, ShoGun, Shark Club, Peking, House of Gyro, Old Country Buffet, The Connaught Place, China Gourmet, Chili's, Outback, The Second Yard, Dunkin' Donuts, PJ Skidoos, The Wave, Brion's Grille, Fairfax Fall Festival
  - Math Department, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mason Day, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Millar Hearing, February 15, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Millar Rallies, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Millar Teach-In, February 1, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minority Affairs, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Motion Pictures, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    "Portrait of a Lady" and "G.I. Jane"
  - Museums, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - North Campus, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Northern Virginia Training Center (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Energy, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Nursing, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Objects, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Computers, Police Cars, Posting Board, Computer Mouse, Beer Bottle, Peanuts, Fruit, Rice, Dollar Bill
  - Ogden, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Outdoors/Nature, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Parking, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Parking Garage Construction, Parking Deck, Parking Lots p
  - Patriot's Day, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Philosophy and Religion Department, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - People-A, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    A; Acosta, U., Adamle, M., Anderson, P., Allen, G., Arnold, T., Alonso, J., Armitage, R., Ailinger,R., Antonavich, P., Aksynov, V., Albriecht,M.
  - People-B, 1980-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Byrd,D., Bush, G., Brown, L. Bernasconi,P., Biden, J., Boyle, M.,Burns, B., Balazsy, A., Berry, F., Bolton,M., Baliles, G., Butler, L., Beavers, H., Burke,C., Bumgardner(Dean), Bagdikian, B., Barry,M., Brutus,D., Belafonte,H., Bailey, S., Bennet,T., Brack, Bondles, A., Bavseh, D., Brown, J
  - People-C, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Clinton, W., Czarda, L., Clark, M., Copperfield, Cronn, Carretla, P.,Cook, Campbell, B., Chisholm, S.
  - People-D, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    D; Di Gennero, Dolan, B., Davenport A., Daniel F., Domzal, T., Dumont, J
  - People-E (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Ebanks, D., Ellig, M., Emanuel, L., Earley, M
  - People-F, 1978-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Fulcher, E., Flecther, J., Farfone, K., Friedan, B., Fukhyann, D., Flecther, J., Fuchs, C., Farris, M
  - People-G, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Gillette, Giroux, Gordon, S
  - People-H, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Hughes, H., Hampson, Hattoy, B., Halberstam, D., Hall, Hughes, C., Horton, T., Hammad, A., Hughes, J., Hawkes, Hogan, A
  - People-I, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Iglesias, J., Ingram, E
  - People-J, 1978-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Jones, W., Johnson, G., Jones., Johnson, A., Jacobs, P., Jones, C., Jensen, R., Jones, S.
  - People-K, 1975-1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Kirkland, C. Krug, R., Keene D., Krusen H., Kizzy J., Kane R., Koestner, K.
  - People-L, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Lewis, Larranaga, J., Lineberger, J., Lamb, B., Lave, Lawless, S., Lipset, S
  - People-M, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Murray, M., Marsalis W., Mann H., McGeehen, J., Malveaux, J., Merten, A., Mason, J., McCarthy, C., Mallon, T., Moran, J., Mobley M., Muir, S., McGrayre S., Mohle, S
  - People-N, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Nestor, E., North, O., Nehemiah, R
  - People-O, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Olmos, E., O'Malley, L., Opala, J., O'Connor, T.,Owens
  - People-P, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Potter, D., Pescole, J., Princess Pale Moon, Pettyjohn, S., Amb. Pashayev Hafiz
  - People-Q, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - People-R, 1979-1997 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Rubin, E., Rossini, Redmond, G., Rothbart, Robb, C., Reno J., Regan, P
  - People-S, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Stewart, J., Scherens, M., Smith C., Smith, S., Sanders,Sekulic, Simorton, A., Swaiey, D., Shugarian, R., Sibler, H., Stevens,B., Shalala D
  - People-T, 1998-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Turner, S., Tapscott, M., Thomas, M., Thorne A., Taylor, A
  - People-U and V, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Vereen, B., Uggams, L
  - People-W, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Westhead, P., Williams, B., Willard, A., Wilkens, R., Wilder, D., Walter, G., Wolf, F., Walters, B., Willis M., Walker, D., Warner, J., Williams, R., Wood, L., Walsch, D
  - Planning and Development, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Political Speakers, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Search, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Profiles, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Programs and Services Offices, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Provost, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Recreation/Sports, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Game Room, Health and Fitness Guide, Hemlock Overlook
  - Registrar's Office, 1975-1980s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Robinson Hall, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Roundtable Discussion, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Security, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Shape, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Shuttle Bus, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Signs, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Snow Scenes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sociology Department, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Speakers, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sports-Baseball, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    GMU vs UConn, GMU vs Uncw, GMU vs JMU, GMU vs ODU, GMU vs UMBC, GMU vs William and Mary, GMU vs NyTech, Head Coach-Bill Brown and Trevor Haqs
  - Sports-Boxing, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sports-Cheerleading, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sports-Coach, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sports-Crew (Rowing), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Sports-Dance (Masonettes and Modern), 1990s (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Sports-Field Hockey, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sports-Football (American), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Football Club, Jackson, E., Coach Football
  - Sports-Golf (M), 1980s (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sports-Judo and Karate, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Sports-Lacrosse (M and W), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Women's LAX vs VT, Women's Lacrosse vs UMBC, ODU and Loyola
  - Sports-Men's Basketball, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Midnight Madness, GMU vs DC Explorers, GMU vs William and Mary, Langley's 1000-PT Ball, GMU vs JMU, Miskiri, J., O'Randall, Anderson, R., Cavey, A., Mc Cants, C., Langley, N.,Redd (Layup), Wanjara, Westhead, Evans, G., Alford, K.
  - Sports-Men's Soccer, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    GMU vs Loyola, Maryland, UNCW, Drexel, VCU, William and Mary
  - Sports-Men's Tennis, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Targott,S., GMU vs George Washinton, St. Mary, East Carolina, American University
  - Sports-Men's Volleyball, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Duckworth,M., GMU vs Juanita, American University, Lewis University
  - Sports-Rugby (M), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sports-Softball, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Adams, A., Alderman, S., GMU vs UNCW, St. Joseph's, UVA, Virginia, Hampton, Southern Charleston, Coastal Carolina
  - Sports-Sport's Fair, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sports-Track and Field (M and W), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Argunes, B., Halla, M., Devers, G.,Mobil Track Meet, Guthrue, D., Amina, Bernabean, S., Achion, J., Aden, I., Baumann, J., Morgan, A., Ogola, F., Cook, J.
  - Sports-Women's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Jay, K., GMU vs William and Mary, VCU, ODU, Kirk,T., Pearson, C.
  - Sports-Women's Soccer, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Willard, GMU VS Maryland, St. Clara, ODU, Villanova, Washington State, Penn, Fresno State, ECU, American University, UNCW
  - Sports-Women's Tennis, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sports-Women's Volleyball, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Kingsley-Ibeh, J., Domokos, V., Kovacs, B., GMU vs WVA, VCU, Maryland, American University, East Carolina and Alumni Game-98
  - 6.1 Sports-Wrestling, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Shea, S., Barlow, R., GMU vs VA Tech, Coppin State, VMI
  - Spring Garden College, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Football Kiosk, Forensics Team Trophies, Student Election Candidates, 3-C Class, Ramadan, President's Roundtable, Pi Kappa Phi, Delta Sigma Pi, Student Senate, StudentLeadership Conference, Greek Sing, Free Tibet Display, English Language Institute, ROTC, Alpha Xi Delta, Chalk The Walk, Pi Kappa Sigma, Chi Omega, Zeta Tau Alpha, Theta Chi, Alpha Phi Karoke, GMU-TV, Kappa Alpha Rush Week, Team Building
  - Students and Campus Activities [1 of 3], 1973-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Pond and Patriot Center, Registrar's Office, Student Union Buildings, St. Robert Bellarmine Chapel, Robinson Hall, Thompson Hall,University Park Townhouses, Science and Tech I, Student Apartment Beating Incident, Call box, Aquatic Center, Krug Hall, Krasnow Institute, Finley Building,Fenwick Library
    Contact Sheets, Color Prints
  - Students and Campus Activities [2 of 3], Late 1970s-Early 1980s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Students and Campus Activities [3 of 3], 1980s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Training, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Series 3: George Mason University Yearbook, 1979-mid 1990s; (6 boxes)
  This series consists of 210 folders which include photographs, contact sheets, and negatives. The images contained in the collection encompass all areas of student life at George Mason University ranging from students on campus to studying, to Greek life and sports, to professors and campus scenery.
  - Baseball, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Basketball, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jenny Beach, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lisa Bradie, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chris Brazda, Lynn Davis, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ken Bumgarner, Arthur Sanders-security, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cabaret, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chess, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jim Conagra, Kathy Pillow, Ronda Jackson, Tom Maschetto, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jean Cotter, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cross country, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Debate team, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Edie Gharaknaian, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Golf team, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Graduation (Nobert Flatow and family), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kathy Judy, Becky McCreight, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Jazz ensemble, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ice skating, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dr. Holt-Psychology, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Begonia Junquern, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ali Kalantari, Diane Southal, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Kevin Kenney-Lopez, Alex Solis, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Law school, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Senator Matsunaga, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Debie McKeeman, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Diane McNulty, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Pasnak-Psychology, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Parking lot, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chris Osbourne, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jerome and Maria Ngeh, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mrs. Murnane, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Jim Morrison, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Doug Meade, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Patriot's Day, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Xan "Ace" Raskin-Photographer, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Residents, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Valerie Rice, Larry Stevenson, Bryan Williams, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mary Carol Sheard, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Soccer, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Jennifer Stone, Jim Velsesz, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Janice Sutera, Career services, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - TKE (Tau Kappa Epsilon), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Marlene Teets, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Volleyball, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tee White, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Wrestling, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Laboratories, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Students, music, faculty, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Various still photos, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - English Department faculty, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Alpha Chi, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Basketball, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Ted Bradley-Biology Department, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Career Services, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cheerleaders, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Chinese visitors, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Cross country, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - GMU Feminists, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Dr. Larry Frazier-Math Department, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dr. Sheryle Friedley-Communications Department, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Honor society, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Aliza Kolder-Sociology Department faculty, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - School of Law, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Mason Day, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Outing Club, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Residents, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Dr. Dan Rothbart-Philosophy, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Soccer, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Softball, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Dr. Michael Sundell-Associate Coordinator of Center for Government, Society, and the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - TKE (Tau Kappa Epsilon), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Tennis, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Volleyball, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Wrestling, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Students, campus, student apartments, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Dance, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Antigone, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Basketball, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Art league, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Chi Omega, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Economics faculty, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Forensics, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Mason/Patriot's Day, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Medievalist Guild, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Phi Mu, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Residents-Student apartments, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Rugby game, November 7 and 14, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Soccer, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tailgate party, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - TKE (Tau Kappa Epsilon), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ZTA (Zeta Tau Alpha), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Students, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New Student picnic, August 28, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Library Tower (Tower 2), Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Judy Miller exhibit, Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Music, Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Arthur Sanders, Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women's soccer, Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Patriot's circle (continuation), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Art, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Astronomy, Physics, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Forensics, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Reeves, President Johnson dedication (WGMU), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Suburbs, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Telecommunications, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Students, faculty, music, athletics, off-campus, ROTC, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Black and White and Color Prints
  - Biology department, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mason Day, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - President home-Guiller House, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Soccer, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - TKE (Tau Kappa Epsilon), 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Modern Dance, December 1, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - American Marketing Association, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dr. Debra Bergoffen, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Business Honor Society, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Geology club, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - W. Terry Hargrave-Decision Sciences, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Softball, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Theta Chi, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Volleyball, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Biology Lab, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Students, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Black and White and Color Prints; Contact Sheets
  - D. Cohen, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Patriot's Day, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Patriot's Day, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Students, University Players, Lecture, campus, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Construction, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Sports-Baseball, Lacrosse, Organizations-Delta Sigma Theta, Accounting club, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Students, campus, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Library, Meetings, Faculty-Dr. Larry Rockwood, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Indoor fair, Decmeber 1986 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - By George!, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - International Week, Music in The Rathskeller, Spring 1988 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Graduation, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Sports/Athletics, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Students, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Faculty, University Police, Buildings and Grounds crew, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Student organizations, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Campus, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - General, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 58)
    contact sheets
  - U.S. Presidents Kennedy and Johnson, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Opening of the Center for Arts, late 1980s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Art, 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Campus, 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A Dance, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arm wrestling, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 5)
    black and white photographs
  - ??? (Delta Sigma Theta) Fashion show, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - International week, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Mason Pageant, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Persian Gulf protest/speech/gathering, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Students, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Students, early 1990s (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Baseball, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Black freshman weekend, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cheerleaders/Cheerleading, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dances, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Football (American), 1990s (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - International week, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Masonettes/Dance team, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Men's soccer, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Patriot center, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rowing and Table Tennis, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 22)
    black and white photographs and Negatives
  - Rugby, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sporting facilities, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sports fans/event facilities, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Dating Game, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Track and Field, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Tree planting/dedication, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - University seal, Faculty, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Various events, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Women's Soccer, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Homecoming "A declaration of Rights", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Graduation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Award ceremony, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Cultural Dance exhibit, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Faculty, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - International week, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - March of Dimes/Walk America/Go for the Gold, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mason week, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Patriot's Ball, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - ROTC repels off Fenwick, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Health Expo, April 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Organization activities, April 1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Homecoming, October 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Campus, December 1992-March 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Campus/Students, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Color Prints and Negatives
  - International week, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Black and white contact sheets, October 1990-December 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Color contact sheets, October 1990-May 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Black and white contact sheets, January 1991-June 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Black and white contact sheets, October 1991-April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Color contact sheets, October 1991-April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Black and white contact sheets, October 1992-November 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Color contact sheets, October 1992-November 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Art/Campus, 1980s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Mason Pageant, Students, early 1990s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Art, Students, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Basketball, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cabaret, Game, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - International week, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Students, Campus, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Students, Campus, Track, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Uplift the Crisis of the Black Male, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Series 4: George Mason University Foundation, 1989; (11 boxes)
  This series contains color negatives and slides depicting GMU student life, campus, faculty, arts, and technology created as part of a fundraising campaign.
  - Arts and Performances, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Color Negatives
  - Campus, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)